{
    "subject": "resource/Laurence_Marks_(British_writer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Goodnight_Sweetheart_(TV_series)",
    "human_readable": "Laurence Marks is known for his work on 'Goodnight Sweetheart'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8579307198524475,
            "question": "What is the title of the work Laurence Marks is known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8332914710044861,
            "question": "What is Laurence Marks known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7582383751869202,
            "question": "Name a work associated with Laurence Marks."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6242882013320923,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in 'Goodnight Sweetheart'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5350143909454346,
            "question": "What is the storyline of 'Goodnight Sweetheart'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48508742451667786,
            "question": "Did Laurence Marks work on any other notable projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4656312167644501,
            "question": "When was 'Goodnight Sweetheart' created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4303430914878845,
            "question": "Where was 'Goodnight Sweetheart' produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.402515172958374,
            "question": "What genre does 'Goodnight Sweetheart' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2999979257583618,
            "question": "Is Laurence Marks a writer or director?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Laurence Marks is known for his work on 'Goodnight Sweetheart'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8702_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does 'Goodnight Sweetheart' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8702_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was 'Goodnight Sweetheart' produced?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8702_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'Goodnight Sweetheart' created?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8702_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8702_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Laurence Marks is known for his work on 'Goodnight Sweetheart'. This information can be found in multiple files, including `58.txt`, `30.txt`, and `70.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}